So here's our setup.
The controller should sit right here.
Here's the transformer.
I took it off.
I'll rewind it a bit.
And I learned something interesting that needs to be done in this coil.
So, our controller is like... Oh, I've got a lot of junk in here.
Yeah, here's the controller.
I modified it.
Here we have two additional knobs that appeared.
But once the schematic is finalized, I think it'll be completely different.
We've got one, two, three, four, five.
Five chips in total.
I tried to keep the number of chips down.
Well, here's our oscillogram.
Yellow trace in blue.
That's on the push-pull.
Purple on the tesla, and this will be on the strobe.
Well, let's see.